Can I have some money ?
I said , " Can I have some money ? "
Kid , how many times do I have to tell you ? I don 't have money .
With a car like this ?
Do you know how many days I worked to buy this car ?
- Whose cat is that ? - It 's mine .
2,191 days .
Dearest ladies with families ...
you care for your households ,
you care for your children ,
your husbands .
And your husband brings home the money .
Congratulations .
But be prepared .
One day , everything changes .
Your husband leaves you ,
finds himself a new wife .
A different woman , a younger woman .
Or perhaps .
Your husband has a stroke and dies .
These things happen .
What 's with you ? Open the door .
Don 't count the things you 've lost .
Let 's count what 's still left .
Look , Hossein ,
I help you , don 't I ?
I give , you take .
Does that seem right to you ?
I swear to God ...
on my mother 's grave , I 'll pay you .
Are you a junkie ?
Answer me .
I 'm sick , I 'm sick .
You 're a junkie .
Your promises mean nothing .
Who made him a junkie ?
What 's your cat 's name ?
Is it a boy or girl ?
Mr. Cat ! Mr. Cat !
He 's really fun .
Look , your father is a normal man .
Gambler , enjoys women .
Takes medicine for his pain .
You see ?
Completely normal . All right ?
However , the things your father likes , he can 't afford .
Right ?
No .
It 's my car , not his .
Do you even realize how much your father owes me ?
I gave you money last week .
Business is business .
Hello ?
Come up here .
I need you .
I want to get really wasted .
We 'll tell Omid to drive .
I don 't get it . Why do they keep having costume parties ?
Seriously .
So what are you going to wear ?
Excuse me , Miss Shaydah ?
I 'm sorry , Miss Shaydah ?
Sorry to bother you , but this is going to take some time to fix .
Go ahead .
Then do you mind leaving me alone in here to work on this ?
What for ?
Your mother and father .
I 'll call you right back .
My mother and father ?
What if they knew you were alone with a boy in your bedroom ?
- Are you serious ? - It 's inappropriate .
What a gentleman .
My knees are weak .
See my car ?
Well , get in .
- How old are you now , Atti ? - Give me my cut .
Take it easy .
Come on , how old are you ?
- Thirty . - Thirty .
You 're getting old .
Don 't you want kids ?
Women want kids , don 't they ?
Get out .
- I want my cut . - You 're light .
- Give me my cut . - Get out .
- I 'm not light . - You think I 'm joking ?
Get out ! Get out of here !
Next time you focus on your job .
Understand ?
And quit your crying .
Hag !
Now what ?
Come on .
Want a line ?
Leave a message , hooker .
It 's Arash , I 'm outside . I 've got something for you .
Look , I want my car .
I should die and leave you in peace .
Here , drink some water first .
You know what would hit the spot ?
Driving in a convertible .
What fun we 'd have .
For God 's sake ,
let 's talk for a minute .
You don 't talk to me .
You don 't look at me .
How much have I given you ?
Should I add it up ?
What do you want , Hossein ?
Let 's talk a little , be close to each other .
When you find some money , come find me .
All right ?
Blind cat .
Are you a good boy ?
Answer me .
Are you a good boy or not ?
Yes .
Don 't lie .
Are you a good boy ?
Yes .
I 'll ask you one more time .
Tell the truth .
Are you a good boy ?
I can take your eyes out of your skull
and give them to dogs to eat .
Till the end of your life ,
I 'll be watching you .
Understand ?
Yes .
Be a good boy .
Dad ...
I brought you soup .
What do I want soup for ?
Don 't you see me ? Do you see me here ?
Where 's your loyalty ?
I 'm sick . Sick !
I need my medicine !
His father is lying here like this , and he 's only thinking of himself .
Arash , look at you .
This is Shirin .
Hey .
Listen , we heard you have X.
Our friend told us to find Dracula .
It 's on me .
Really ?
To your health .
Your costume is really fun .
- Are you scared ? - Very scared .
And you ? Are you scared ?
So this is your new job ?
- Give me another one . - One is enough .
- Give it . - One is enough .
Open your mouth .
Are you scared ?
This pill is nothing without you .
It needs you .
Arash !
Look how chic he is now .
Arash , are you okay ?
Arash ?
I 'm lost .
Where are we ?
Bad City .
Bad City ?
I live in Bad City .
This doesn 't look like Bad City .
Does it ?
It 's not familiar .
I 'm Dracula .
Don 't worry , I won 't hurt you .
Can I ask you something ?
Why are you here ?
Both of us -
Both of us are here .
I 've never felt like this before .
Give me your hand .
You 're so cold .
Let 's sit .
You can 't sit here .
My house is near here .
You can sit there .
I can 't , I have to sit .
What 's with you ?
You look funny .
I 'm tired .
Yes , I can see that .
Where were you in the middle of the night ?
With a girl .
What girl ?
I don 't know her name .
You don 't know her name .
Who 's her family ?
I don 't know .
" I don 't know , I don 't know . "
Are you an idiot now ? Have you become an idiot ?
Yep , he 's an idiot .
Congratulations , handsome .
Why are you following me ?
What do you want ?
Where did you get this ?
Girl , where did you get this ?
Have one .
They 're sweet .
What are you following me around for ?
Are you religious or something ?
No .
Look who found her tongue .
You want to do what I do ?
It 's not easy .
If that 's why you 're following me around , I 'm not a teacher .
You don 't like what you do .
You 're watching me ?
At night .
So ...
what did you see all this time watching me ?
You 're sad .
You don 't remember what you want .
You don 't remember wanting .
It passed long ago .
And nothing ever changes .
Idiots and rich people
are the only ones who think things can change .
You 're saving your money .
For what ?
Are you a thief ?
No .
So what are you ?
MEET ME AT THE POWER PLANT TOMORROW AT 10 : 00 P.M. - DRACULA
Are you hungry ?
I brought you a hamburger .
You don 't like hamburgers ?
I never met someone who didn 't like hamburgers .
I don 't know your name .
You don 't know me .
Obviously . We just met .
What was the last song you listened to ?
" Hello , " " Hello . "
Lionel Richie .
Sad .
Sad songs hit the spot , don 't they ?
I know something else about you .
Your ears aren 't pierced .
They 're pretty .
They 're for you .
Too bad you can 't wear them .
Seriously ?
Are you sure ?
Did it hurt ?
- You don 't have to . - Do the other one .
- Forget it . - Do it .
It 's done .
What lucky earrings .
I 've done bad things .
I 'm bad .
Obviously .
You don 't know the things I 've done .
And you don 't know the things I 've done .
If there was a storm coming right now ,
a big storm , from behind those mountains ,
would it matter ?
Would it change anything ?
Did you come here to watch me ?
Are you watching me ?
What do you want ?
What ?
What ? What do you want ?
You 're still torturing me ?
You left me here alone . Now you 're back again .
What the hell do you want from me ?
Leave me alone ! You ruined me !
This is the life you left me !
Leave me alone !
What the hell do you want from me ?
What are you doing ?
Come here , look .
Look at its eyes . It 's your mother .
- Have you lost your mind ? - Do you see its eyes ?
It 's your mother . Look , look .
Look at this place .
Why do you do this ?
Can you tell me ? How much of this am I supposed to take ?
- What do you want me to do ? - You 're supposed to be my father !
I don 't even know what I 'm doing anymore .
I don 't know what I 'm doing anymore !
You want your medicine ?
Here .
Take it and get out of this house .
Take it and leave this house , and don 't come back .
Take the cat with you . I don 't want it anymore .
I want you to dance for me ...
like the old days .
I want -
I want to watch you .
Atti , sweetheart ...
come here .
Let 's be together .
Sit right here .
Let 's have a good time .
No , I don 't want to .
I said I don 't want to , Hossein . I don 't want to .
Atti , sit down .
I said , " Sit down . "
We 're going to have a good time .
I said , " I don 't want to . " Do you hear me ?
Let 's have a good time .
Do you hear me , Hossein ?
We 're going to have a good time together .
Let 's go .
You have to leave .
Take that thing with you .
Boy , if you saw something , you have to tell me .
Understand ?
- Did you see something ? - No .
Did you see someone ?
No .
- Who was it ? - I don 't know .
Who was it ?
What do you mean , you don 't know ?
I don 't know .
We have to go .
Pack your things .
Do you have a bag ?
Look , I can 't stay here .
We 'll get in my car and go .
Let 's leave Bad City .
Come with me .
Don 't leave me . Don 't leave me alone .